Kheel, Theodore W. Arbitration files 6021/003
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- TWU Local 100 (Floretta Gilliam) and NYCTA, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- TWU Local 100 (Christopher Williams) and NYCTA, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- TWU Local 100 (Ronald Donovan, et al.) and NYCTA, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- TWU Local 100 (Bart Giaime, et al.) and NYCTA, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- TWU Local 100 (Luigi Bascetta) and NYCTA, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  Feb 19
- TWU Local 100 (John O'Roarke) and NYCTA, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- TWU Local 100 (Linda Sommerville, et al.) and NYCTA, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 27)
- TWU Local 100 (John Parengan, et al.) and NYCTA, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 28)
- TWU Local 100 (James Liverpool, et al.) and NYCTA, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  March 11
- TWU Local 100 (Ronald Gori, et al.) and NYCTA, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 30)
- TWU Local 100 and NYCTA, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 31)
- TWU Local 100 (Arthur Brown, et al.) and NYCTA, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 32)
- TWU Local 100 (Charles Saumer, et al.) and NYCTA, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  April 15
- TWU Local 100 (Elinora Durham) and NYCTA, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 34)
- TWU Local 100 (James Brogdon, et al.) and NYCTA, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  April 19
- TWU Local 100 (Daniel Suazo) and NYCTA, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  Sept 14
- TWU Local 100 (George Rodriguez, et al.) and NYCTA, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  Nov 24
- TWU Local 100 (Eric Samuels) and NYCTA, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  Aug 25
- TWU Local 100 (Henry Cassati, et al.) and Parochial Bus System, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  Jan 24 - June 25
- TWU Local 100 (Irving Sharp) and Parochial Bus System, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 40)
- TWU Local 100 (Joseph Morgan) and Parochial Bus System, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 41)
- TWU Local 100 and Parochial Bus System, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  April 6
- TWU Local 100 and Parochial Bus System, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 43)
- TWU Local 100 (Juan Mendoza) and Parochial Bus System, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 44)
- TWU Local 100 and Parochial Bus System, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 45)
- TWU Local 100 and Parochial Bus System, 1965-1969 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  Feb 25, 1965 - Dec 16, 1969
- TWU Local 100 (William Burell) and Parochial Bus System, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 47)
- TWU Local 100 (Martin Tate) and Parochial Bus System, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  March 16
- TWU Local 100 (Efrain Gonzalez) and Parochial Bus System, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  March 12
- TWU Local 100 (Arnell Williams Exam) and Parochial Bus System, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  Nov 10
- TWU Local 100 (Richard Carter) and Parochial Bus System, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 51)
- TWU Local 100 (Herman Leroy Geddis) and Parochial Bus System, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 52)
  Dec 17
- TWU Local 100 and Parochial Bus System (Box 15, Folder 53)
- TWU Local 100 (Robert Hachmeyer) and Parochial Bus System, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 54)
- TWU Local 100 and Queens - Nassau Transit Lines (Thomas Dalley), 1956 (Box 15, Folder 55)
- TWU Local 100 (D.C. O'Shea) and Queens Surface Corp., 1992 (Box 15, Folder 56)
- TWU Local 100 and Queens Surface Corp., 1992 (Box 15, Folder 57)
- TWU Local 100 and Queens Surface Corp., 1992 (Box 15, Folder 58)
- TWU local 100 (William Curran) and Queen Surface Corp., 1994 (Box 15, Folder 59)
- TWU Local 100 (Donald McDermott, et al.) and Queens Surface Corp., 1994 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- TWU Local 100 (Patricia Hines) and Queens Surface Corp., 1994 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- TWU Local 100 (Frank Sicuranza) and Queens Surface Corp., 1994-1995 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  Oct 31, 1994 - Nov 15, 1995
- TWU Local 100 (Francisco Matos) and Queens Surface Corp., 1995 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- TWU Local 100 (Yvonne Rennie) and Queens Surface Corp., 1995 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- TWU Local 100 (R.L. Williams) and Queens Surface Corp., 1995 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- TWU Local 100 (Horace Willis) and Queens Surface Corp., 1996 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- TWU Local 100 (Martin Dominick) and Queens Surface Corp., 1996 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- TWU Local 100 (Alan Wishnoff) and Queens Surface Corp., 1996 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- TWU Local 100 (Edward Milano) and Queens Surface Corp., 1996-1997 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  Sept 18, 1996 - Aug 5, 1997
- TWU Local 100 and Queens Surface Corp., 1997 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  March 19
- TWU Local 100 and Queens Surface Corp., 1997 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- TWU Local 100 (Howard Webb) and Queens Surface Corp., 1998 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  Sept 2
- TWU Local 100 (Robert Ware, et al.) and Queens Surface Corp., 1998 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- TWU Local 100 and Queens Transit Corp. (Arthur Haggerty, et al.), 1959 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- TWU Local 100 and Queens Transit Corp. (James McGowan - Suspension for Non-Attendance), 1959 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Transit Industry Queens Transit Corp. Agreements, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  Dec 1
- TWU Local 100 and Queens Transit corp. (Richard Johnson, et al.), 1960 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- TWU Local 100 (John gordon, et al.) and Queens Transit Corp., 1960 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- TWU Local 100 (Peter Woloschuk, et al.) and Queens Transit Corp., 1962 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- TWU Local 100 (Christopher Lyne) and Queens Transit Corp., 1963 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- TWU Local 100 (William Dunn, et al.) and Queens Transit Corp., 1963 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- TWU Local 100 and Queens Transit Corp. (Working Conditions & Schedules), 1964 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- TWU Local 100 and Queens Transit Corp. (Schedules), 1964 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- TWU Local 100 (Fred Ellis) and Queen transit corp., 1964 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- TWU Local 100 and Queens Transit corp. (Holiday Pay), 1964 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- TWU Local 100 (John McQuade) and Queens Transit Corp., 1965 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- TWU Local 100 and Queens Transit Corp.(Subcontracting and Holiday Party), 1966 (Box 16, Folder 28)
- TWU Local 100 (Thomas McLaughlin, et al.) and Queens Transit Corp., 1967 (Box 16, Folder 29)
- TWU Local 100 (Richard Foster-Discharge) and Queens Transit Corp., 1971 (Box 16, Folder 30)
- TWU Local 100 (Patrick Ferguson - Vacation Allowance) and Queens Transit Corp., 1973 (Box 16, Folder 31)
- TWU Local 100 and Queens Transit Corp. (Frank Jacinski), 1974 (Box 16, Folder 32)
- TWU Local 100 and Queens Transit Corp. (Henry Tomkalski, deceased), 1975 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  May 1
- TWU Local 100 and Queens Transit Corp. (Vacation Pick), 1975 (Box 16, Folder 34)
- TWU Local 100 (W.H. Looper - Retirement Benefits) and Queens Transit Corp., 1977 (Box 16, Folder 35)
- TWU Local 100 and Queens Transit Corp. (James Gilligan), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 36)
- TWU Local 100 and Queens Transit Corp. - Misc., 1979 (Box 16, Folder 37)
- TWU Local 100 (Richard Reynolds - Vacation) and Queens Transit Corp., 1980 (Box 16, Folder 38)
- TWU Local 100 (Julio Hernandez) and Queens Transit Corp., 1980 (Box 16, Folder 39)
- TWU Local 100 and Queens Transit Corp. Overhaul and Rebuilding Work by "B" Mechanics on 2 "benches" in Maintenance Dept, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 40)
- TWU Local 100 (John Ferry) and Queens Transit Corp., 1981 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  March 4
- TWU Local 100 (Robert Fogel) and Queens Transit Corp., 1981 (Box 16, Folder 42)
- TWU Local 100 (Richard Reilly, et al.) and Queens Transit Corp., 1981 (Box 16, Folder 43)
- TWU Local 100 and Queens Transit Corp. (George Sauer, et al.), 1981 (Box 16, Folder 44)
- TWU Local 100 (John Swift) and Queens Transit Corp., 1987 (Box 16, Folder 45)
- TWU Local 100 and Queens Transit Corp. (Daniel Marines III), 1982 (Box 16, Folder 46)
- TWU Local 100 and Queens Transit Corp. (Summer Pick), 1982 (Box 16, Folder 47)
- TWU Local 100 and Queens Transit Corp. (Wayne Cercielo, et al.), 1983 (Box 16, Folder 48)
- TWU Local 100 and Queens Transit Corp. (McEntee, Sean), 1983 (Box 16, Folder 49)
- TWU Local 100 and Queens Transit Corp. (William Hastings), 1983 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  July 18
- TWU Local 100 and Queens Transit Corp. (William Cody, et al.), 1983 (Box 16, Folder 51)
- TWU Local 100 and Queens Transit Corp. (Noxroy Scott, et al.), 1983 (Box 16, Folder 52)
- TWU Local 100 and Queens Transit Corp. (Hess, et al.), 1983 (Box 16, Folder 53)
- TWU Local 100 and Riverdale Transit Corp. Alan Jackson, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  Feb 12
- TWU Local 100 and Riverdale Transit Corp. John Flanagan, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- TWU Local 100 and Riverdale Transit, Inc. John Kennedy, et al., 1983 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- TWU Local 100 and Riverdale Transit Corp. Osborne Wright, et al., 1983 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- TWU local 100 and Scarsdale Bus Corp. Nicholas DeBene, et al., 1960-1967 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  May 17, 1960 - March 10, 1967
- TWU Local 100 and Scarsdale Bus Corp. Pat Mango, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- TWU Local 100 and Scarsdale Bus corp. Interpretation of Control Provisions re: School Recesses, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- TWU Local 100 and Scarsdale Bus Corp., 1961 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- TWU Local 100 and Scarsdale Bus corp. Elmer Edwin Sprucer, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- TWU Local 100 and Scarsdale Bus Corp. and Scaresdale School Bus Comp. Emanuel J. LaBarbera, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- TWU Local 100 and Scarsdale Bus Corp. DeBene, et al., 1966 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- TWU Local 100 and Scarsdale Bus Corp. Nicholas DeBene, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- TWU Local 100 and Scarsdale Bus Corp. John Fantini, et al., 1974 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- TWU Local 100 and Scarsdale Bus Corp. Cecil Labeach, et al., 1982 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  Jan
- TWU Local 100 and Scarsdale Bus Corp. General Corresp., 1987 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- TWU Local 100 and Steinway Transit Corp. Union Objection to Proposed Schedules, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- TWU Local 100 and Steinway Transit Corp. Employees refusal to complete picking of schedules that co. has posted, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- TWU Local 100 and Steinway Transit Corp. Schedules Re: Combination of runs, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- TWU Local 100 and Steinway Transit Corp., 1969 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- TWU Local 100 and Steinway Transit Corp., 1976 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- TWU Local 100 and Steinway Transit Corp. Rajko Kopilas, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- TWU Local 100 and Steinway Transit Corp. Arbitration involving rescheduling shifts in maintenance dept., 1979 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- TWU Local 100 and Steinway Transit Corp. - John Connell, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- TWU Local 100 and Steinway Transit Corp. Anthony Coyle, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- TWU Local 100 and Steinway Transit Corp. Joseph Petty, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  July 26
- TWU Local 100 and Steinway Transit Corp. Hang Lui, et al., 1978 (Box 17, Folder 26)
- TWU Local 100 and Steinway Transit Corp. Hung Lui, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 27)
- TWU Local 100 and Steinway Transit Corp. William Owens, et al., 1980 (Box 17, Folder 28)
- TWU Local 100 and Steinway Transit Corp. Hung Lui, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  Dec 19
- TWU Local 100 and Steinway Transit Corp. William Owens, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 30)
- TWU Local 100 and Steinway Transit Corp. Miscellaneous (Box 17, Folder 31)
- TWU Local 100 and Steinway Transit Corp. William Henry, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  Mar 3
- TWU Local 100 and Steinway Transit Corp. Frank Rivera, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 33)
- TWU Local 100 and Steinway Transit Corp. Raffale Franco, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 34)
- TWU Local 100 and Steinway Transit Corp. Philip Ferrera, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 35)
- TWU Local 100 and Steinway Transit Corp. Charles Stivala, et al., 1984 (Box 17, Folder 36)
- TWU Local 100 and Steinway Transit Corp. Stolen Tools, etc., 1954 (Box 17, Folder 37)
- TWU Local 100 and Surface Transit Corp. Terminal Facilities and Slow Down, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  Oct 8
- TWU Local 100 and Surface Transit Corp. Jacob Berry, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 39)
- TWU Local 100 and Surface Transit Corp. Patrick Doyle, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 40)
- TWU Local 100 and Surface Transit Corp. Robert Franklin, et al., 1960 (Box 17, Folder 41)
- TWU Local 100 and Surface Transit Corp. Milton Goldstein, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 42)
- TWU Local 100 and Surface Transit Corp. Joseph Hynes, et al., 1960 (Box 17, Folder 43)
- TWU Local 100 and Surface Transit Corp. Robert Kirby, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  Nov 1
- TWU Local 100 and Surface Transit Corp. Ruben MacDonald, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 45)
- TWU Local 100 and Surface Transit Corp. Tony Paparesta, et al., 1960 (Box 17, Folder 46)
- TWU Local 100 and Surface Transit Corp. Joseph Perotta, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  Aug 2
- TWU Local 100 and Surface Transit Corp. Leroy Smith, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  June 19
- TWU Local 100 and Surface Transit Corp. John Walsh, et al., 1960 (Box 17, Folder 49)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Notes, 1949-1980 (Box 17, Folder 50)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro coach corp., 1952 (Box 17, Folder 51)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp., 1952 (Box 17, Folder 52)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Newspaper Clippings, 1952 (Box 17, Folder 53)
  Feb 15
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Agreements, 1953-1982 (Box 17, Folder 54)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Passenger Problem, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 55)
  April 25
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Michael Kuzmiak, et al., 1959 (Box 17, Folder 56)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Frank Meechan, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 57)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. contract and Paid Swing Time, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 58)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Correspondence and Memoranda, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 59)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Lost Payment Claims, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 60)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Lost Payment Claims, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 61)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Gerard Kelly, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 62)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Anthony Bonanno, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 63)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Ralph Flecha, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 64)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Frank Santa, et al., 1963 (Box 17, Folder 65)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. James Dean, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 66)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Anthony Corrado, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 67)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp.Joseph McGuire, et al., 1964 (Box 17, Folder 68)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Position Vacancy, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 69)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Holiday Pay, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 70)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Holiday Pay, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 71)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Holiday Pay, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 72)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Correspondence and Memoranda, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 73)
  Dec 30
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Position Vacancy and Senority, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 74)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. William Perry, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 75)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Night shift Discrimination, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 76)
  May 26
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Robert Stalf, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 77)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Extra Copies & Drafts, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 78)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Albert Young, et al., 1966 (Box 17, Folder 79)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Frank Roehl, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 80)
  May 3
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Jesse Duncan, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 81)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Maurice Santos, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 82)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Dominick Basile, et al., 1968 (Box 17, Folder 83)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Christopher Pappas, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 84)
  Nov 6
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Mr. I Lanuto, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 85)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Fred Novellino, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 86)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. David Jones, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 87)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. James Newberry, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 88)
  dec 8
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Marshall Alston, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 89)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Marshall Alston, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 90)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Decisions, 1978-1981 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Hubert Florius, et al., 1980 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  Oct 31
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Original Awards, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Frank Cirgliano, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Ugrading Mechanics, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Willie McClain, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Richie Ventura, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Lawrence Davis, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Tadeo Velazquez, et al., 1982 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Correspondence and Memoranda, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Re: Money Changing work by dispatches, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Salvador Ottonmanelli, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  May 2
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Richard Patti, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. James Newberry, et al., 1982 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Vincent Ferullo, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Re: Drug and Alcohol Program, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Re: Nathaniel Crump, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  March 8
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Claude Hudson, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Swapping Runs, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Bus Repairs, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. R. Pointer, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Ralph Payal, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Michael Mannarino, et al., 1997 (Box 18, Folder 23)
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Carmine Gizzi, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 24)
- Walter Sanford, et al., 1998 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  June 30
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Mack Holley, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  Nov 30
- TWU Local 100 and Triboro Coach Corp. Regina Kilgore (Box 18, Folder 27)
- TWU Local 100 and Westchester Street Transportation co. Job Duties, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 28)
- TWU Local 100 and Westchester Street Transportation co. Gerald Canavan, et al., 1979 (Box 18, Folder 29)
- TWU Local 100 and Westchester Street Transportation co. Raymond de LaRosa, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 30)
- TWU Local 100 and Westchester Street Transportation co. Michael Donaghy, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 31)
- TWU Local 100 and Westchester Street Transportation co., Inc. Joseph Donoghue, et al., 1965 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  Aug 26
- TWU Local 100 and Westchester Street Transportation co. Roger Finan, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  Oct. 8
- TWU Local 100 and Westchester Street Transportation co. Patrick French, et al., 1980 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  June 4
- TWU Local 100 and Westchester Street Transportation co. Willie Gordon, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  Feb 6
- TWU Local 100 and Westchester Street Transportation co. Thomas Insidori, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 36)
- TWU Local 100 and Westchester Street Transportation co. Walter Kennedy, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 37)
- TWU Local 100 and Westchester Street Transportation co. Andrea Lewis, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 38)
- TWU Local 100 and Westchester Street Transportation co. Joseph Maddox, et al., 1977 (Box 18, Folder 39)
- TWU Local 100 and Westchester Street Transportation co. John Magnis, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 40)
- TWU Local 100 and Westchester Street Transportation co. Edward Meaney, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 41)
- TWU Local 100 and Westchester Street Transportation co. Samuel Patterson, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 42)
- TWU Local 100 and Westchester Street Transportation co. Samuel Patterson, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 43)
- TWU Local 100 and Westchester Street Transportation co. James Reilly, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 44)
- TWU Local 100 and Westchester Street Transportation co. John Roberts, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 45)
- TWU Local 100 and Westchester Street Transportation co. Claudie Santiful, Jr., 1977 (Box 18, Folder 46)
- TWU Local 100 and Westchester Street Transportation co. Walter Smith, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 47)
- TWU Local 100 and Westchester Street Transportation co. Miscellaneous (Box 18, Folder 48)
- TWU Local 100 and Yankees Bus Company William Reed, et al., 1951 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  Nov 16
- TWU Local 100 and Yankees Bus Company Joseph A. Ford, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 50)
  Feb 4
- TWU Local 100 and Yankees Bus Company Salvatore DiPaolo, et al., 1954 (Box 18, Folder 51)
- TWU Local 100 and Yankees Bus Company Dominick Moran, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 52)
- TWU Local 100 and Yankees Bus Company Frank Ostapchuk, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 53)
- TWU Local 100 and Yankees Bus Company Kenneth Clark, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 54)
- TWU Local 100 and Yankees Bus Company 2 year Agreement, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 55)
- TWU Local 100 and Yankees Bus Company John Keane, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 56)
- TWU Local 100 and Yankees Bus Company Joseph Sparno, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 57)
- TWU Local 100 and Yankees Bus Company Martin Cannon, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 58)
- TWU Local 100 and Yankees Bus Company Henry Davis, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 59)
- TWU Local 100 and Yankees Bus Company Robert Letterio (Box 18, Folder 60)
- TWU Local 100 and Yankees Bus Company William Miller, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 61)
- TWU Local 100 and Yankees Bus Company Constitutions (Box 18, Folder 62)
- TWU Local 10 and Surface Transit Corp. and Fifth Ave Coach Lines - Re: Introduction of one-way street, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- TWU Local 10 and Surface Transit Corp. and Fifth Ave Coach Lines Re: One-way traffic, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  June 17
- TWU Local 10 and Surface Transit Corp. and Fifth Ave Coach Lines change Resulting from One way traffic, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- TWU Local 10 and Surface Transit Corp. and Fifth Ave Coach Lines Frank Corcoran, et al., 1960 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- TWU Local 10 and Surface Transit Corp. and Fifth Ave Coach Lines Pension Claims, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- TWU Local 10 and Surface Transit Corp. and Fifth Ave Coach Lines Pension, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- TWU Local 10 and Surface Transit Corp. and Fifth Ave Coach Lines, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- TWU Local 100 and Liberty Lines Express and Liberty Lines transit, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- TWU Local 100 and Liberty Lines Express and Liberty Lines transit (Box 19, Folder 9)
- TWU Local 100 and Liberty Lines Transit and Liberty Lines Express Hugh Ruden, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- TWU Local 100 and Liberty Lines Express and Liberty Lines Transit, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- TWU Local 100 and Liberty Lines Express and Liberty Lines Transit, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- TWU Local 100 and NYCTA and MABSTOA Health and Welfare Plan, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- TWU Local 100 and NYCTA and MABSTOA Two-way Radio, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Transport Workers Union Local 100 and NYC Transit Authority, Manhattan and Bronx Surface Operating authority and TWU - NYC Transit Authority Health Benefit Trust and TWU - MABSTOA Health Welfare, and Death Benefit Trust, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- TWU Local 100 and NYCTA and MABSTOA, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Transport workers Union of America AFL-CIO Local 100 and New York City Transit Authority, Manhattan and Bronx surface Transit Operating authority, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Transport workers Union of America Local 100 AFL-CIO and New York Transit Authority, Manhattan and Bronx Surface Transit Operating authority, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Transport workers Union of America Local 100 AFL-CIO and New York Transit Authority, Manhattan and Bronx Surface Transit Operating authority (Box 19, Folder 19)
- TWU Local 100 and Queens Transit Corp. and Steinway Omnibus Corp. (Felix McCullough and Overtime), 1964 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- TWU Local 100 and Queens Transit corp. and Steinway Transit Corp. (Section 33 of contract, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 21)